{
    "subject": "Victor_Emmanuel_III_of_Italy",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Elena_of_Montenegro",
    "human_readable": "Victor Emmanuel III of Italy is married to Elena of Montenegro.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9532380104064941,
            "question": "Who was Victor Emmanuel III of Italy married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8901408314704895,
            "question": "What is the name of Victor Emmanuel III of Italy's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8797894716262817,
            "question": "Elena of Montenegro was married to whom?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8424880504608154,
            "question": "Was Victor Emmanuel III of Italy married to a foreign royal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7809905409812927,
            "question": "Which royal figure was married to Elena of Montenegro?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.561871349811554,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Elena of Montenegro?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5059731602668762,
            "question": "What was the name of the queen consort of Italy during Victor Emmanuel III's reign?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5023084282875061,
            "question": "To whom did Victor Emmanuel III of Italy tie the knot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43561670184135437,
            "question": "Who was the king of Italy during Elena of Montenegro's time as queen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1601613610982895,
            "question": "Who held the position of king during Elena's time as queen consort?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Victor Emmanuel III of Italy is married to Elena of Montenegro.",
            "html": "yago_21722_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was the king of Italy during Elena of Montenegro's time as queen?",
            "html": "yago_21722_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom did Victor Emmanuel III of Italy tie the knot?",
            "html": "yago_21722_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name of the queen consort of Italy during Victor Emmanuel III's reign?",
            "html": "yago_21722_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21722_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21722_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21722_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21722_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21722_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21722_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21722_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21722_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21722_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21722_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents contain information about Queen Elena of Montenegro being the wife of King Victor Emmanuel III of Italy, which supports the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Queen Elena of Montenegro was the wife of King Victor Emmanuel III of Italy."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}